angellearning.com 2009-12-24

# ANGEL Learning -- Privacy Policy

As of May 14, 2008

ANGEL Learning is committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete AngelLearning.com Privacy Policy.

## Collecting Your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ( **“Personal Information”** ) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you fill out the ANGEL Demo Request Form or the ANGEL Software Request Form. 

When you request a demo or software, we will ask you to register electronically. When you do, we keep registration information on file with any information you’ve already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This is considered your personal profile. 

## Use of Your Personal Information

We use your personal information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find services or information on AngelLearning.com.
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from ANGEL Learning.

ANGEL Learning will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ANGEL Learning or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ANGEL Learning, and (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AngelLearning.com, or the public. 

## Control of Your Personal Information 

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, ANGEL Learning will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

ANGEL Learning may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues related to a demo, software or service you requested. 

## Changes To Your Personal Information 

If you ever need to change information in your personal profile, or if you would like to unsubscribe to updates about our services and products, you may send us an email with the change of information or other request, to [info@angellearning.com](mailto:info@angellearning.com).

## Security of Your Personal Information 

ANGEL Learning strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. 

## Changes to This Statement 

ANGEL Learning will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Policy, ANGEL Learning will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Web site. 

## Contact Information 

ANGEL Learning welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by em-mail at [info@angellearning.com](mailto:info@angellearning.com), or postal mail.

Copyright © 2009 ANGEL Learning. All rights reserved. U.S. Patent Numbers: 6,988,138; 7,493,396, 7,558,853.
